

Ana Luisa Araújo

Miticulous planner, ambitious learner and a rising leader

Personal information

Address

Smedegade 59E - Horsens

Email

aanaluaraujo@gmail.com

Telephone

+45 93899509

Birthday

6th of May, 1997

Competences

Revit



Analysis and Problem solvying



Sketching



Planning and docummentation



Communication and management



Language

Portuguese - Native

English - C1

Danish - B2

Profile

Originally from Brazil, I have so far lived in 4 different countries and the experience I have gained and still do is unexchangable.

I like to think of myself as a carismatic and warm problem solver and leader. I thrive in problematic situations where I am put in control in order to find a solution.

I flourish the most in instances where I can use my planning and docummentation skills to bring order and clear goals to the work that should be done.

Education

Via University College • Horsens

Architectural Technology and Construction Management 2021 - 2024

I am now in my 4th semester as an ATCM student. Since the first semester I have been gaining knowledge and developing skills regarding Building Design, Building Services, Structural Design, Communication and Building Planning and Management. I have understanding of the different phases of a building project such as Outline Proposal, Project Proposal, Regulatory and Tender phases.

I also have aquired knowlege regarding construction and mounting phases.

During this education I have been able become an advanced Revit user and became familiar with terms like BIM and XR technology.

Law school • Brazil

2014 - 2016

I started a bachelor degree in Law in 2014 and decided to quit in 2016. During those 2 years of education, I studied amongst others, much sociology and philosophy which allowed me to learn different perceptions of society and human behaviour.

Work experience

Waitress • Tequila Sunrise

Part time

July 2021 - July 2022

I worked as a waitress for a Mexican restaurant in Horsens, mostly as a summer job. This was a great experience for me to practice my Danish with complete strangers and under pressure.

Unskilled replacement in care • Nørrevang Plejehjem

Part time

July 2021 - January 2022

I worked as a carer for the elderly at a plejehjem in Horsens. It was my best work experience so far, because I got to meet and care for so many beautiful and kind elders. Here I learned much about resilience and purpose.

Au Pair

September 2017 - September 2019

I had the opportunity of living with a danish family for 2 years. I helped caring for their day to day lives and kids. During this time I was able to dedicate a lot of time to studying Danish and learning about the danish culture and traditions

Store assistant • Red Cross Malmö

Part time

September 2020 - December 2020

I lived in Malmö for almost 1 year, and during my time there I was a volunteer at Red Cross Malmö. I was a store assistant and got to meet and work with people from many different nationalities and backgrounds.

English teacher • CCAA

Part time

August 2014 - March 2017

My first job experience was as an English teacher at a private english school in Brazil. I got to teach kids from age 5 to adults of maximum age 65.

In these years as a teacher I learned soft skills that were much needed to teach people that were beginners in English.